<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Industries on ServiceFolder</title>
    <link>https://www.servicefolder.com/industries.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Industries on ServiceFolder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.servicefolder.com/industries/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pool service software that helps you manage your pool service business and helps for servicing, dispatching, estimating, and scheduling | ServiceFolder</title>
      <link>https://www.servicefolder.com/industries/pool-service-software.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.servicefolder.com/industries/pool-service-software.html</guid>
      <description>HomeIndustriesPool Service SoftwarePool Service Software: Pool service software for swimming pools and swimming pool automationWhat is Pool Service software?Pool service software is a type of computer application that automates scheduling, routing,dispatching, invoicing, and customer tracking for swimming pools. It focuses on the unique needsof pool upkeep and features include scheduling, dispatching, reporting, and more.Manage your invoices and collect payments for completed work with a pool service software solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Handyman Software for Home Maintenance for servicing, dispatching, estimating, and scheduling | ServiceFolder</title>
      <link>https://www.servicefolder.com/industries/handyman-software.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.servicefolder.com/industries/handyman-software.html</guid>
      <description>HomeIndustriesHandyman SoftwareHandyman Software for Home MaintenanceWhat is Handyman Software?The Handyman Software is a software tool that helps small-scale repair service businessesautomate job scheduling and billing. It includes tools such as managing work orders, creatinginvoices, processing payments, and even connecting with customers.The Handyman Software is a tool that companies use to manage the day-to-day schedule for their crew.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contractor software for servicing, dispatching, estimating and scheduling | ServiceFolder</title>
      <link>https://www.servicefolder.com/industries/contractor-software.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.servicefolder.com/industries/contractor-software.html</guid>
      <description>HomeIndustriesContractor SoftwareContractor software for servicing, dispatching, estimating and schedulingWhat is Contractor Software?Contractor software provides solutions to handyman and contractorsandallows them to optimize the management and implementation of the services throughautomation.Contractor Software for Scheduling and ManagementContractor scheduling software is an easy to use tool that integrates with QuickBooks. This isacost-effective option for companies who want to manage their Contractor installation serviceand scheduleit effectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Electrician software for electrical contractors | ServiceFolder</title>
      <link>https://www.servicefolder.com/industries/electrician-software.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.servicefolder.com/industries/electrician-software.html</guid>
      <description>HomeIndustriesElectrical Contractor SoftwareElectrician software for electrical contractorsWhat is Electrician Software?Electrician software helps a company streamline their business with efficient scheduling anddispatching electricians. Most importantly, it saves time by making the process of findingqualified electricians easier for employers.What is electrical contractor software?Electrical contractor software provides an all-in-one field management solution. This includesestimating and invoicing templates, time tracking, mileage tracking, payroll integration, invoicegeneration, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HVAC software for servicing, dispatching, estimating and scheduling | ServiceFolder</title>
      <link>https://www.servicefolder.com/industries/hvac-software.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.servicefolder.com/industries/hvac-software.html</guid>
      <description>HomeIndustriesHVAC SoftwareHVAC software for servicing, dispatching, estimating and schedulingWhat is HVAC Software?HVAC software provides solutions to heating, ventilation and air-conditioning contractorsandallows them to optimize the management and implementation of the services throughautomation.HVAC Software for Scheduling and ManagementHVAC scheduling software is an easy to use tool that integrates with QuickBooks. This isacost-effective option for companies who want to manage their HVAC installation serviceand scheduleit effectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lawn Care Software for servicing, dispatching, estimating, and scheduling | ServiceFolder</title>
      <link>https://www.servicefolder.com/industries/lawn-care-software.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.servicefolder.com/industries/lawn-care-software.html</guid>
      <description>HomeIndustriesLawn Care SoftwareLawn Care software for servicing, dispatching, estimating and schedulingWhat is Lawn Care Software?Lawn Care software provides solutions to landscaping, fertilization and leaf raking techsandallows them to optimize the management and implementation of the services throughautomation.Why Choose ServiceFolder Software for Lawn Care?ServiceFolder is the field service management software solution for small businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Servicing, dispatching, estimating and scheduling software for Plumbing business | ServiceFolder</title>
      <link>https://www.servicefolder.com/industries/plumbing-software.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.servicefolder.com/industries/plumbing-software.html</guid>
      <description>HomeIndustriesPlumbing SoftwareServicing, dispatching, estimating and scheduling software for Plumbing businessWhat is Plumbing Software?Plumbing software is a set of tools that automate scheduling, dispatching and billing. This typeof software makes it easy for techs to estimate plumbing jobs and bill customers on-site from amobile tablet (mobile device). It also allows them to communicate with the customer in real timeto provide information about what they will be doing, when they will be coming out, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tackling Appliance Repair with Appliance Repair Software | ServiceFolder</title>
      <link>https://www.servicefolder.com/industries/appliance-repair-software.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.servicefolder.com/industries/appliance-repair-software.html</guid>
      <description>HomeIndustriesAppliance Repair SoftwareTackling Appliance Repair with Appliance Repair SoftwareWhat is Appliance Repair Software?Appliance service software is a tool that allows businesses to run more efficiently by managingthe logistics of their business. With online payment and invoicing, you can offer moreconvenient options for customers. There are also features that allow management teams to keep aneye on the progress of repairs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
