<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog-no-sidebars on ServiceFolder</title>
    <link>https://www.servicefolder.com/blog-no-sidebar.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog-no-sidebars on ServiceFolder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.servicefolder.com/blog-no-sidebar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Service Franchise Software  | Service Management Software App </title>
      <link>https://www.servicefolder.com/service-franchise-software.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.servicefolder.com/service-franchise-software.html</guid>
      <description>Why start looking for a software providing branches and franchise features? Business grow and as part of growing pains, software is vital to run and expand the business across multiple locations. ServiceFolder offers easy to expand solutions for Field Service companies. Franchisor will be given distinct permissions and at the same time the headoffice has complete view of the data.
What can ServiceFolder provide value Franchises/Branches? Franchisor has a ready system operating in the cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Service Management Software  | Free Service Management Software App </title>
      <link>https://www.servicefolder.com/what-is-service-management-software.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.servicefolder.com/what-is-service-management-software.html</guid>
      <description>Imagine this.
You have a product manufacturing business and produce thousands of products that have to be taken stock of, billed and delivered to different customers, checked for maintenance and repairs, etc. And, for this task, you assign two very efficient field technicians whom you trust and are also quick at their task. But the disadvantage is, they have to file everything manually without using an organized software.
So, in this situation, who do you think can make mistakes easily and miss out on essential details and how long would it take for the company to identify, which technician’s job is accurate?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Field Service Management Software  | Free Field Software App </title>
      <link>https://www.servicefolder.com/what-is-field-service-management-software.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.servicefolder.com/what-is-field-service-management-software.html</guid>
      <description>For businesses that offer services carried out on the job site, keeping a close eye over how your employees perform in the field is vital to your business&amp;rsquo;s success. Managing multiple employees in the field can be challenging, mainly depending on your business&amp;rsquo;s nature.
Field service management software offers multiple features and capabilities that allow you to optimize managing your employees in the field. You can achieve several functions through quality service management software, allowing you to further your business.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
